Jeanne L. Noble Papers, 1955-2002
Sophia Smith Collection
Jeanne L. Noble papers
1955-2002
Noble, Jeanne, L.
MS 488
36 boxes (15.5 linear ft.)
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
Professor, Author. Papers consist primarily of materials related to Noble's involvement in the National Council of Negro Women (specifically the Dorothy I. Height Leadership Institute) in the late 1990s, and the Delta Sigma Theta sorority in the 1980s and 1990s. In addition, there are some materials documenting Noble's work on several governmental commissions and committees in the 1960s and 1970s, as well as various community organizations. Also included are essays and speeches by Noble and drafts and typescripts for her book, Beautiful, Also, Are the Souls of My Black Sisters: A History of the Black Woman in America (1978). There is little personal material.
Jeanne Laveta Noble was born on July 18, 1926 in West Palm Beach, Florida, the first of four children of Floyd and Aurelia Noble. Floyd Noble left the family in the early 1930s, and Aurelia Noble moved the family to Albany, Georgia, where she operated a custom drapery business and taught drapery making at the Albany Area Vocational School. Aurelia Noble's mother, Maggie Brown, played an important role in helping to raise the Noble children.
Jeanne Noble earned a B.A. in psychology and sociology from Howard University in 1946, then an M.A. from Columbia University in 1948. She fell in love with teaching during a two-year appointment (1948-50) at Albany State College, in Albany, Georgia. From 1950 to 1952, Noble was dean of women at Langston University in Langston, Oklahoma. She returned to Columbia in 1952 to continue graduate study in educational psychology and counseling psychology, earning her Ph.D. in 1955.
For her dissertation and first book, The Negro Woman College Graduate (published in 1956), Noble examined the lives of 1,000 African-American women graduates who had been out of college at least five years. An early nonfiction book written by an African-American woman about African-American women for a white audience, it was one of the first studies to consider gender in concert with race. The work won the Pi Lambda Theta, National Association for Women in Education Research Award.
Noble held various research assistant and administrative posts, including Assistant Dean of Students, at City College before joining the faculty at New York University around 1959, teaching first in the Department of Educational Sociology of the Center for Human Relations and later in the School of Education. In 1960 she and co-author Margaret Fisher published College Education as Personal Development, a book written to be used in college orientation courses by first-year college students.
Outside of the classroom, Noble served on many boards and commissions. From 1958 to 1963 she was national president of the sorority, Delta Sigma Theta, Inc., a public service organization she joined while an undergraduate at Howard University. Noble later served Delta as Chair of its Arts and Letters, and Rituals and Ceremonies Commissions.
From 1960 to 1963 Noble served on the Defense Advisory Committee of the U.S. Department of Defense. In 1962 she was part-time director of Training for the Harlem Domestic Peace Corps. She was appointed to the Committee on Federal Employment of the President's Commission on the Status of Women in 1963. In 1964 Sargent Shriver asked Noble to serve on a committee to develop plans for a Girls' Job Corps. She was also on the board of directors of the Urban League of Greater New York, the Girl Scouts of the U.S.A., and the National Social Welfare Assembly.
In the late 1960s Noble began work on the book Beautiful, Also, Are the Souls of My Black Sisters: A History of the Black Woman in America. Described by Noble as a "psycho-social look at black women," the book was eventually published in 1978.
In 1972 Noble took a leave of absence from NYU to function as Executive Vice President of the National Council of Negro Women under a grant from the Ford Foundation and the Rockefeller Foundation.
Around 1975 Noble moved from NYU to Brooklyn College of the City College of New York where she taught in the education department, eventually becoming a professor of guidance and counseling in the graduate school.
Noble ventured into television, appearing on "The Learning Experience," a weekly educational show broadcast in New York City in 1977 and served as co-host of "Straight Talk" in the summer of 1979.
In 1996 Noble helped to launch the Dorothy I. Height Leadership Institute of the National Council of Negro Women with funding from the W.K. Kellogg Foundation. The Institute was conceived to foster a cadre of young leaders to assist traditional African-American women's organizations to meet the challenges of the 21st century. For a variety of reasons, the Institute was not able to sustain funding once its initial three-year grant was exhausted.
In addition to her teaching, Noble also had a small fashion design business and worked as an educational and organizational consultant.
Jeanne L. Noble died of congestive heart failure after a long battle with breast cancer on October 17, 2002.
The Jeanne L. Noble Papers consist of 15.5 linear ft. dating from 1955 to 2002 and are primarily materials related to Noble's involvement in the National Council of Negro Women (specifically the Dorothy I. Height Leadership Institute) in the late 1990s, and the Delta Sigma Theta sorority in the 1980s and 1990s. In addition, there are some materials documenting Noble's work on several governmental commissions and committees in the 1960s and 1970s, as well as various community organizations. Also included are essays and speeches by Noble and drafts and typescripts for her book, Beautiful, Also, Are the Souls of My Black Sisters: A History of the Black Woman in America (1978). There is little personal material.
Types of materials include appointment books, audiotapes, awards, clippings, correspondence, essays, magnetic disks, memorabilia, notes, photographs, proposals, publications, reports, speeches, and videotapes.
This collection is organized into nine series:
I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS AND PHOTOGRAPHS
II. CORRESPONDENCE
III. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES
IV. SPEECHES
V. WRITINGS
VI. SUBJECT FILES
VII. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS AND COMPUTER MEDIA
VIII. ARTIFACTS
OVERSIZE MATERIALS
The Papers are open to research according to the regulations of the Sophia Smith Collection without any additional restrictions. Original audiovisual materials are closed to research. Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual materials for which there is no use copy should contact the Sophia Smith Collection to discuss options.
The Jeanne L. Noble Papers were donated to the Sophia Smith Collection in 2003 by Alma Noble and Charlice Noble-Jones.
Afro-American women-History--20th century--Sources; African American women--Education--History--20th century--Sources; African American women in the professions--History--20th century--Sources; African American women--Biography--Sources; African American women--Societies and clubs--History--Sources; Delta Sigma Theta Sorority--History--Sources; Dodson, Dan W., 1907-; National Council of Negro Women--History--Sources; Noble, Jeanne L.
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS AND PHOTOGRAPHS 1955-2002, undated, 2.75 linear ft.
  The bulk of this series consists of appointment books kept by Jeanne Noble from 1958 to 2002. There is also a small amount of general biographical material about Noble and her mother, Aurelia Noble, and financial records. In addition, there are some materials about her affiliation with Church of the Ascension in New York City, and some organizational development training. The photographs are of Jeanne Noble, some of her friends and associates, and Delta Sigma Theta and National Council of Negro Women events.
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE 1957-2002, undated, .25 linear ft
  This small series consists of congratulatory correspondence received by Noble when she was appointed to the committee to develop plans for a Girls' Job Corps in 1964, plus a small amount of correspondence from some noted friends and associates, including Lillian Benbow, Edith Green, Alex Haley, Patricia Roberts Harris, Lena Horne, and Barbara Jordan.
- SERIES III. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES 1950-2002, undated, 5.75 linear ft.
  By far the largest series, included here are records of Noble's work teaching and in administration in colleges and universities, her work as a leadership/organizational development consultant, and her voluntary service. The bulk of the materials relate to her work for the Delta Sigma Theta Sorority in the 1980s and 1990s, and the National Council of Negro Women in the late 1990s. The materials are arranged alphabetically by organization name.
- SERIES IV. SPEECHES late 1950s-2001, 1.75 linear ft.
  This series consists of texts, drafts, notes, and presentation materials for speeches and workshops given by Noble to a variety of groups. As a frequent speaker, Noble often reworked texts or portions of speeches for use in different venues. Where a complete text with title and date of delivery is available, the materials are arranged chronologically. These are followed by undated texts filed alphabetically. At the end of the series are fragments of speeches arranged by subject and several folders of "ideas" and notes for speeches. There is also a small amount of correspondence about booking speeches and arranging travel. Noble also assisted friends and colleagues with speeches and there are also a few texts by others with her annotations.
- SERIES V. WRITINGS1957-99, undated, .75 linear ft.
  This series consists of correspondence, contract and permissions materials, drafts, notes, reviews, and publicity for Noble's 1978 book, Beautiful, Also, Are the Souls of My Black Sisters. The materials give a sense of her struggle to get the book published. Copies of articles and typescripts of other writings by Noble dating from the 1960s to the 1990s are also included.
- SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES1960s-2000, undated, 1 linear ft.
  This series consists of clippings, playbills, notes, reports, and articles on individuals and subjects of interest to Noble. The bulk of the materials date from the 1980s and 1990s. They are arranged alphabetically by subject.
- SERIES VII. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS AND COMPUTER MEDIA1969-98, undated, 1 linear ft.
  This series consists primarily of audio and video recordings of Delta Sigma Theta or National Council of Negro Women meetings, conventions, and performances. Original audiovisual materials are closed to research. Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual materials for which there is no use copy should contact the Sophia Smith Collection to discuss options. There are also 3 ½ inch computer disks (3 ½") which appear to contain files from the 1990s.
- SERIES VIII. ARTIFACTS1958-97, undated, 1 linear ft.
  Materials in this series are primarily related to Noble's many honors and awards dating from the 1950s to the 1990s. Materials include plaques, commendations, keys to cities, and other items.
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS, 1.25 linear ft.
  Oversize materials consist primarily of honors related to Noble's service on various boards, committees, and commissions. There is also a small amount of material related to teaching and a couple of posters.
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS AND PHOTOGRAPHS
  - General, 1955-2002, undated (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Curriculum vitae, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Address and telephone books, undated (Box 1, Folder 5-8)
  - Apartment, 4 Washington Square Village, 1966-84 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Appointment books
    - 1958-1960/61 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - 1961/62-75 (Box 2, Folder 1-9)
    - 1975/76-86 (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
    - 1987-93 (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
    - 1994-2002 (Box 5, Folder 1-6)
  - Church of the Ascension in the City of New York
    - General, 1978-2000, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Inquirers Class, 1988, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Search Committee, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
    - Task Force on Racism and Cultural Diversity, 1993-96 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Vestry, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Family: Aurelia Pritchard Noble [mother], 1984-90 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Financial
    - General, 1979-92, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Jeanne Noble Fashions, Ltd., 1986-87 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Jeanne Noble Associates, 1981, 1987, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Legal, 1983-87 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Medical/dental, 1981-2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Photographs
    - Jeanne L. Noble
      - Alone, 1996-97 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - With others, 1960s, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Delta Sigma Theta
      - General, 1992, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Unidentified event, 26 Sep 1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Friends and associates, 1971, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - National Council of Negro Women, 1977, 1997, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Training
    - Texaco Management Institute, May 1998 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Situational Leadership, Sep 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - Travel diaries, 1957, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - General, 1957-2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 6-9)
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE
  - Congratulatory on appointment to committee to develop plans for a Girls' Job Corps, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
  - Shirley Barnes, 2000-02 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Lillian Benbow, 1982-83 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Albert Crum, 1986, 1988, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dan Dodson, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Judith Dollenmayer, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Edith Green, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Alex Haley, 1968-72 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Patricia Roberts Harris, 1971-82 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Lena Horne, 1965-66, 1990, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Barbara Jordan, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- SERIES III. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES
  - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater Foundation, 1978-98, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - American Council on Education, Commission on College Students, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Awards for Excellence in Corporate Community Service, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - City University of New York
    - Brooklyn College
      - General, 1984, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Education 712.2, Study of School, Community and Institutions, spr 1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Education 775.1, Educational Administration and Supervision, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Education 775.2x, Administration: Theory and Practice, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - City College, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Planning Committee for Doctoral Studies in Education, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Common Cause, National Governing Board, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Dance Theater of Harlem, Inc., 1998-2001, undated (Box 8, Folder 21-22)
  - Delta Sigma Theta, Inc., [see also Speeches and Writings]
    - General, 1978-2002, undated (Box 8, Folder 23-24)
    - Chapters
      - Alpha, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Baton Rouge, Sigma Alumnae Chapter, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Detroit Alumnae, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Gamma Psi Sigma (Albany, GA), 1950 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - New York Metropolitan, 1990-2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Commission on Arts and Letters (CAL)
      - General, 1973, 1986-95, undated (Box 9, Folder 6--8)
      - Demetria McClain's notebook, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - African-American Cultural Odyssey project, 1991-92, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Artist Resource Directory, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Black Arts Renaissance: A Celebration of Excellence, 1988, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Board presentation materials, 1991? (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Convention
        - 1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
        - Ecumenical Service, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
        - 1992
          - General (Box 9, Folder 16)
          - Planning (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Ecumenical Service in honor of Bishop Barbara Clementine Harris, Eastern Region, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Manual, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Multi Cultural Education Initiative, 1992, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - NAACP Image Awards CAL statement, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Project Cherish
        - General, 1992,1997, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
        - Baltimore Alumnae Chapter Project Cherish Celebration, 16 May 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1988-92 (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
      - Scripts, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service (SITES), "Field to Factory: Afro-American Migration, 1915-1940," 1986-90 (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
      - South Atlantic Regional Conference Arts and Letters Luncheon, 22 Jun 1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Video production
        - Public Service Announcement, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
        - "Seventy-Five Years in Retrospect: Destiny Begins Today," 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Workshops
        - South Atlantic Regional Conference, Workshop, Jun 1991 (Box 10, Folder 16)
        - Southwest Regional Conference, Jul 1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Commission on Ritual and Ceremonies
      - General, 1990-2000, undated (Box 10, Folder 18-20)
      - Meetings, 1996, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
      - Board presentation materials, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Delta Protocol and Traditions Workshop, Southwest Regional Conference, Aug 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Initiation Ceremony script, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Jewel Ceremony, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Membership Intake Training, 1982-83
        - General, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - Pilot phase, 1982-83 (Box 11, Folder 8)
        - Proposed ceremonies, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - Notes and presentation materials, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Notebook, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
      - Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Omega Omega Service, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Reports, 1996-97 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Ritual Revision Committee
        - General, 1982, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
        - Drafts, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
        - Forewords, 1996, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
        - Typescripts, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Sharon Lettman Pacheco (designer of print materials), 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Survey, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Sylvette Long (designer of robes, stoles, t-shirts), 1990-92 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Workshops at Regional Conferences, 1997
        - General (Box 12, Folder 4)
        - Eastern (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Committees, 1990, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Confidential memo to Yvonne Kennedy, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Constitution and bylaws
      - Revisions, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Published versions, 1998, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Convention
      - 30th, Baltimore, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - 32nd, Atlanta, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - 40th, Miami Beach, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - 41st, Baltimore, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - 42nd, St. Louis, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - 43rd, Orlando, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - 44th, New Orleans, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - 45th, Chicago, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Delta Research and Education Foundation (DREF), 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - DST Telecommunications, Inc.
      - General, 1974-79, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 4-7)
      - Film, "Countdown at Kusini," 1976-88 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Eastern Region Torches, 1993-96, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Eastern Regional Conference, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Executive Board
      - General, 1991-98, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Transition checklists, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Forms, blank, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Founders
      - Osceola McCarthy Adams, 1974-75, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Lillian Benbow, 1976-94, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Anna Johnson Julian, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Invitations to Jeanne Noble, 1988-97, n..d. (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - General (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Gloria Beverly, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Howardena Pindell, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Honorary Members
        - General, 1989, 2000, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
        - Induction materials, 1988-92, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
        - Nominees, 2000, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Memorabilia (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Presidential Task Force on Secrets, Symbols and Protocol, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Presidential Report by Jeanne Noble, 15 Aug 1960 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Publications
      - Center for Research on African American Women Journal, Jul 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Chapter mailings, 1990, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
      - Delta Sigma Theta, Inc. Corporate Report, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Delta Journal, 1985/86; spr 1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Membership Intake Program, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 12-13)
      - Official Ritual
        - 1988-89 (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
        - 1991, 1996, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
      - "Protocol and Traditions Manual," 1997 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - "Profile," 1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - "Pyramid Syllabus," 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Newsletters, 1971, 1981, 1985, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - "Toward New Horizons," 75th Anniversary booklet, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Rosters, 1984/85, 1996/97, 1997/98, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Web site, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Yancey Commission, 1959-63, undated (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
  - DeWitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund "Pathways To Teaching" Project
    - General, 1995-97 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Evaluation by Jeanne L. Noble
      - Final report, January 1997 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Drafts (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Courses, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Mentors, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Mentor log, Marcelle Maxwell, 1995-96 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - DeWitt Wallace-Reader's Digest Fund "Pathways To Teaching" Project (cont'd)
    - Questionnaire for administrators, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Questionnaire for participants, 1995-96 (Box 16, Folder 2-5)
  - Girl Scouts USA, Board of Directors and Governance Task Group, 1963, 1998-2002, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Harlem Youth Opportunities, Associated Community Teams (HARYOU-ACT), Board of Directors, 1965-66 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
  - International Center for Integrative Studies (ICIS), 1990-92, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Jersey City, NJ, Guidance Department: teaching materials, circa 1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - National African American Women's Leadership Institute, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - National Council of Negro Women (NCNW)
    - General, 1987, 1990, 1998-2000, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Annual report, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Bethune Program Development Center, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Board orientation, Oct 1999 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Bylaws, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Campus Sections list, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Congress of National Black Churches Leadership Conference, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Dorothy I. Height Leadership Institute (DIHLI)
      - General, 1996-99, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Program proposals (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1997-99 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        - Faculty, 1997-99 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
        - Dorothy I Height, 1996-99 (Box 17, Folder 4)
        - Jane E. Smith, 1998-99, undated (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
        - Karen Stanley, 1998-99 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Affiliate organizations of NCNW
        - Leadership Summit, 10-13 Oct 1997
          - General (Box 17, Folder 8)
          - Participant bios (Box 17, Folder 9)
          - Notebook (Box 17, Folder 10-12)
        - Meeting, "Unity in 2000," 23 May 1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
        - National Affiliates Assembly, 11-13 Dec 1998 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - College Student Academy
        - General, 1998-99, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)